SUMMARY

I design & develop cross-platform software with a focus on clear visual communication, natural user input, and trend-agnostic, painless product experiences.

Pulling from a diverse professional background I architect custom & cohesive solutions to each project that cater to the unique and evolving needs of both client & end-user.

PROFICIENCY

Development

HTML5, Pug, CSS3, SASS Node, Express, Vue, Babel Jquery, Handlebars, Moment Linux, Apache, PHP, SQL, C#

Design & Animation

Photoshop, Illustrator XD, InvisionApp, Sketch, Gliffy After Effects, Premiere, FCPX Unity3D, Maya

Project Management

Git, Subversion Pivotal, Jira, Trello, Asana, Slack MS/Libre/Open Offices

Marketing & Testing

Google Analytics, Matomo (Piwik)
Adwords, Tag Manager, Search Console
Salesforce, Hubspot, Insightly
Mailchimp, Campaign Monitor
Visual Website Optimizer

EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer, Designer, Animator - Mursion, Inc.

May 2016 - Present

I produce hi-fidelity interactive wireframes & prototypes and lead UX/design planning for emerging mobile, web, and native software. I develop responsive SPAs in NodeJS for web-based product and Unity3D interfaces in C# for native software.

Products I design and develop include: video recording analytics, session booking & management calendars, system profiling & verification, user and client management, and simulation control HUDs.

Additional roles include: guiding offshore teams in company design spec & software interfacing, consulting with the sales team for lead generation, SEO, analytics, CRM, & marcom, and providing QA for software release, security, testing, & client support

Marketing Designer, Web Developer - Element-360

Sept. 2014 - May 2016

I handled all client-branded visuals and web development including image & HTML5 ad creation, landing page campaigns, email communication design & coding, behaviour/heatmap analysis, and technical SEO auditing for 40+ national real estate communities.

I developed internal tools to facilitate SEO, campaign reporting, CRO, and user experience. Led A/B and multivariant testing campaigns in market research, design planning, and client reporting. Regularly audited performance of image/text ads, and conversion rate & organic search improvements.

EXPERIENCE

(continued

Contract UX Designer - ThingFace

Aug. 2014 - Sept. 2014

I developed internal tools to facilitate SEO, campaign reporting, CRO, and user experience. Led A/B and multivariant testing campaigns in market research, design planning, and client reporting. Regularly audited performance of image/text ads, and conversion rate & organic search improvements.

Game Artist, Animator, Video Editor - The Littlest Golfer, Inc.

Apr. 2013 - Aug. 2014

I led art direction for 2D mobile game created in Unity3D and sold on the App Store and Google Play. I created the UI, tiling environment textures, character animations spritesheets, designed puzzle-based levels, and image ads for the game release.

Additionally, working in a small team to create a 3D Animated Pilot children's show I:

- Designed, modeled, rigged, and animated characters
- Handled all editing, compositing, and motion-graphics within After Effects
- Created promotional print materials for the show premiere

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Arts - New Media

Univertity of North Carolina at Asheville Concentration in 3D Animation Graduated 2012